Thy kingdom come. Thy will be done.
The Boondock Saints is a action, thriller, crime film directed by Troy Duffy.
Tired of the crime overrunning the streets of Boston, Irish Catholic twin brothers Conner and Murphy are inspired
by their faith to cleanse their hometown of evil with their own brand of zealous vigilante justice.
As they hunt down and kill one notorious gangster after another, they
become controversial folk heroes in the community.
But Paul Smecker, an eccentric FBI agent, is fast
closing in on their blood-soaked trail.
Paul Smecker, played by Willem Dafoe.
Conner MacManus, played by Sean Patrick Flanery.
Murphy MacManus, played by Norman Reedus.
Rocco, played by David Della Rocco.
Il Duce, played by Billy Connolly.
Detective Dolly, played by David Ferry.
The Boondock Saints II: All Saints Day is a 2009 vigilante action thriller film written and
directed by Troy Duffy, based on a story he co-wrote with his brother Taylor.
A sequel to The Boondock Saints (1999), the film stars Sean Patrick Flanery, Norman
Reedus, Clifton Collins Jr., Julie Benz, Peter Fonda, and Billy Connolly.
Set eight years after the events of the first film, it follows Irish fraternal twin brothers Connor and Murphy MacManus
(Flanery and Reedus) living a quiet life in Ireland with their father Noah, formerly known as "Il Duce" (Connolly).
However, when an assassin frames the twins for the murder of a Catholic priest, they return to Boston and join forces with Mexican
underground fighter Romeo (Collins, Jr.) and FBI Special Agent Eunice Bloom (Benz), a former protégée of Paul Smecker.
The Boondock Saints II: All Saints Day had its world premiere in Boston on October 19,
2009, and was theatrically released in the United States on December 11, 2009.
Despite negative reviews from critics, the film was a modest success at the box
office, grossing $10.6 million against its $8 million budget.
A sequel is currently in development, with
Flanery and Reedus expected to return.
The film explores themes of bratva (russian mafia), boston,
massachusetts, detective, irish-american, prologue.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.